# ANDY CHECO

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### CONTACT



(917) 736-0925



🔀 andycheco25@gmail.com 🔗



💳 checoandy.com 🔗



github.com/savedcity @



in linkedin.com/in/andy-checo 🔗

### TECHNICAL SKILLS

- JavaScript, JQuery, React
- Python, DJango
- CSS, Sass, Bootstrap
- HTML
- REST APIs
- Node.js, Express.js
- JWT, Firebase, Bcrypt, **Express Session**
- MongoDB, Mongoose
- SQL, PSQL, SQLite
- · Bash, Git, Github

## **EDUCATION**

### **General Assembly**

Mar 2021 - June 2021 Software Engineer Immerse

## NYC College Of Technology

August 2016 - June 2017 Art In Advertisement

### **PROFILE**

I've always been driven by technology and it's potential, and software engineering is a field that pushes me to bring that potential out. With my past experience, multitasking, time management, and great detail work is where I thrive the most. My greatest achievements are the projects I've built which are an image of my abilities, uniqueness and proficiency so I take a lot of honor in them. I am beyond thrilled to be starting in a field where I'll be doing what I love.

### **PROJECTS**

### Spamazon 🔗

- An e-commerce app with features like CRUD, authentication, and full cart functionality including a mock purchase.
- Used: React (class comp), Javascript, PSQL, Python, Django, HTML, CSS, and full authentication with Firebase.

#### Reviewt 🔗

- Created an app with the idea of having users post reviews on their most favorite (or hateful) products.
- Used: Javascript, JQuery, EJS, HTML, CSS, MongoDB, Mongoose, Express, and full authentication with express session and bcrypt.

#### myHome ∂

- A realtor app where you can find, as well as list, homes in the southern states
- Used: React (functional comp), Javascript, MongoDB, Express, HTML, CSS, and full authentication with JWT and Bcrypt.

More projects on my portfolio

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Software Engineer Fellow

**General Assembly** 

3 months | 2021 - 2021

- Learned various software languages, frameworks, libraries and tools.
- Completed projects, tasks, and assignments using skills learned.
- Worked alongside other classmates in order to complete projects and assignments as well as working together with Github while communicating accurately.

#### Remote Customer Service Agent

Various projects including Apple and HBO 2 Years | 2019 - 2021

- Opened and maintained customer accounts by recording account information
- Maintained financial accounts by processing customer adjustments
- Prepared product or service reports by collecting and analyzing customer information
- Meeting personal/team sales targets and call handling quotas